<jobs>
    <job>
        <id>45699</id>
        <categories/>
        <company>
            <website>
                <![CDATA[ http://www.sup46.com/ ]]>
            </website>
            <id>272</id>
            <name>
                <![CDATA[ SUP46 - Start-Up People of Sweden ]]>
            </name>
            <industry>
                <![CDATA[ Startup ]]>
            </industry>
            <logo>
                <![CDATA[ https://media-eu.jobylon.com/companies/company-logo/sup46-start-up-people-of-sweden/sup46logo.17dfebf5.png ]]>
            </logo>
            <cover>
                <![CDATA[ https://media-eu.jobylon.com/companies/company-cover/sup46-start-up-people-of-sweden/members-2800-320x200.021a4561.jpg ]]>
            </cover>
            <slug>
                <![CDATA[ sup46-start-up-people-of-sweden ]]>
            </slug>
            <descr>
                <![CDATA[ <p>Startup hub SUP46 offers a member based community and is home to Sweden’s next startup stars. Thanks to the world-class ecosystem of investors, mentors and partners we provide our members with a competitive advantage.</p> ]]>
            </descr>
        </company>
        <contact>
            <photo/>
            <phone>
                <![CDATA[ +46703802603 ]]>
            </phone>
            <email>
                <![CDATA[ sebastian@sup46.com ]]>
            </email>
            <name>
                <![CDATA[ Sebastian Fuchs ]]>
            </name>
        </contact>
        <departments/>
        <title>
            <![CDATA[ Head of Startups and Community ]]>
        </title>
        <slug>
            <![CDATA[ head-of-startups-and-community ]]>
        </slug>
        <descr>
            <![CDATA[ <p>SUP46 Startup People of Sweden is one of the world’s leading startup hotspots, as Spotify, King, Mojang, and Skype are just a few of the countless global mega successes that have come out of Sweden. Even so, its startup community long felt the absence of a centrally located meeting place and a natural forum for likeminded startup people. SUP46 gathers only the most exciting and innovative digital startups, backed by top VCs, business angels, corporates, and accelerator partners. The result is a startup community of the highest standard. Since the launch in October 2013 the community has seen what network and knowledge sharing can do for boosting international growth. </p> <p>As Head of Startups and Community you are working for the members, to make sure they get the most of their membership with us. <br> You are the face and voice of the Community and will ensure that we assist our members in becoming global game changers. </p> <p>You will have the great responsibility to build on the SUP46 network and represent SUP46's brand and culture and to attract great startups with game changing potential. </p> <p>You will have a variety of weekly, monthly and ad hoc tasks, and deal with many different actors within the startups scene such as:<br> Members, Alumni, Partners, Sponsors, Mentors, Service Providers and other Community Supporters. </p> <p><strong>Your main tasks will be:</strong></p> <ul> <li> <p>Further developing our Membership offering</p> </li> <li> <p>Further developing our HUB offering: Workspace, Café, Event and Conference</p> </li> <li> <p>Communication towards our members including writing monthly newsletters, internal communication and communicating events etc </p> </li> <li> <p>Organizing internal events (workshop, community breakfast, networking lunch, founders dinners, founder hours; pitch training, celebrating holidays…) from confirming dates with partners to writing and sending out invitations and reminders as well has ordering catering and taking care of guests </p> </li> <li> <p>Sit with members and give them advice and support with their pitch decks/pitching</p> </li> <li> <p>Facilitate introductions for our members to investors, partners and other startups etc</p> </li> <li> <p>Organize Community Intro/on-boarding and off-boarding, making sure all new members have been on-boarded, introduced to the community, given welcome packs and are up to date with the services we offer </p> </li> <li> <p>Support in reviewing service providers and putting them up on our platform</p> </li> <li> <p>Gather feedback from the Community via the Community Pulse</p> </li> <li> <p>Manage HUB P&amp;L and Community Budget </p> </li> <li> <p>Answer emails from external people as well as request from members </p> </li> <li> <p>Other Ad Hoc tasks and willingness to travel in Sweden when necessary</p> </li> </ul> ]]>
        </descr>
        <function>
            <![CDATA[ All functions ]]>
        </function>
        <experience>
            <![CDATA[ Experienced ]]>
        </experience>
        <employment_type>
            <![CDATA[ Full-time ]]>
        </employment_type>
        <from_date>2019-08-28</from_date>
        <to_date/>
        <language>
            <![CDATA[ en ]]>
        </language>
        <locations>
            <location>
                <text>
                    <![CDATA[ Stockholm, Sweden ]]>
                </text>
                <city_short>
                    <![CDATA[ Stockholm ]]>
                </city_short>
                <country_short>
                    <![CDATA[ SE ]]>
                </country_short>
                <city>
                    <![CDATA[ Stockholm ]]>
                </city>
                <area_1>
                    <![CDATA[ Stockholm County ]]>
                </area_1>
                <place_id>
                    <![CDATA[ ChIJywtkGTF2X0YRZnedZ9MnDag ]]>
                </place_id>
                <url>
                    <![CDATA[ https://maps.google.com/?q=Stockholm,+Sweden&ftid=0x465f763119640bcb:0xa80d27d3679d7766 ]]>
                </url>
                <country>
                    <![CDATA[ Sweden ]]>
                </country>
                <area_1_short>
                    <![CDATA[ Stockholm County ]]>
                </area_1_short>
            </location>
        </locations>
        <video>
            <content/>
            <url/>
        </video>
        <urls>
            <apply>
                <![CDATA[ https://emp.jobylon.com/applications/jobs/45699/create/ ]]>
            </apply>
            <ad>
                <![CDATA[ https://emp.jobylon.com/jobs/45699-sup46-start-up-people-of-sweden-head-of-startups-and-community/ ]]>
            </ad>
        </urls>
        <skills>
            <![CDATA[ <ul> <li>You are a social person and a strong team player</li> <li>Knowledge about startups and the startup scene and network in Stockholm/Sweden</li> <li>Ability to multitask, be flexible and thrive in a busy environment</li> <li>Great at working by yourself and be a good networker and matchmaker</li> <li>Enjoy meeting and helping people with relevant information</li> <li>Computer literate and experience using tools such as Slack, Mailchimp etc</li> <li>Organized and creative minded</li> <li>You speak &amp; write English at a native level - Swedish is a great plus</li> <li>Investor/VC experience is beneficial</li> </ul> ]]>
        </skills>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>7161</id>
        <categories/>
        <company>
            <website>
                <![CDATA[ https://kry.se/ ]]>
            </website>
            <id>382</id>
            <name>
                <![CDATA[ KRY ]]>
            </name>
            <industry>
                <![CDATA[ Startup ]]>
            </industry>
            <logo>
                <![CDATA[ https://media-eu.jobylon.com/companies/company-logo/kry/12028784_909346472481867_4639286357079341408_o.712ec284.png ]]>
            </logo>
            <cover>
                <![CDATA[ https://media-eu.jobylon.com/jobs/company-cover/qa-manager/img_9146.5272db3c.JPG ]]>
            </cover>
            <slug>
                <![CDATA[ kry ]]>
            </slug>
            <descr>
                <![CDATA[ <p><em><strong>Join us in making healthcare better and more accessible to all!</strong></em></p> <p>KRY is a service where patients meet healthcare professionals through their phone or tablet.</p> <p>We who work at KRY want to build better and more accessible healthcare by moving it online and by providing a service that gives the patient the best possible health care experience. We already have tens of thousands of happy users in Sweden and are now expanding internationally.</p> ]]>
            </descr>
        </company>
        <contact>
            <photo>
                <![CDATA[ https://media-eu.jobylon.com/main_contact/kry_2780_2.daa9e7b0.jpg ]]>
            </photo>
            <phone/>
            <email>
                <![CDATA[ joachim@kry.se ]]>
            </email>
            <name>
                <![CDATA[ Joachim Hedenius ]]>
            </name>
        </contact>
        <departments/>
        <title>
            <![CDATA[ QA Manager ]]>
        </title>
        <slug>
            <![CDATA[ qa-manager ]]>
        </slug>
        <descr>
            <![CDATA[ <p>You will:</p> <ul> <li>Be in charge of quality assurance for our product across all markets.</li> <li>Work closely together with our product and development teams, helping them to succeed in delivering a great user experience.</li> <li>Be in charge of test and release planning.</li> <li>Define and build the overall QA strategy and team over time.</li> </ul> <p>At KRY we work in an agile way with short iterations and focus heavily on continuous improvement of our product, tools and processes. You will play an important part in this, ensuring that our teams continuously improve the way they work with quality.</p> <p>KRY is a rapid growing startup so expect the scope and responsibilities of this role to grow at a high pace!</p> ]]>
        </descr>
        <function>
            <![CDATA[ Quality Assurance & Test ]]>
        </function>
        <experience>
            <![CDATA[ Experienced ]]>
        </experience>
        <employment_type>
            <![CDATA[ Full-time ]]>
        </employment_type>
        <from_date>2016-12-02</from_date>
        <to_date/>
        <language>
            <![CDATA[ en ]]>
        </language>
        <locations>
            <location>
                <text>
                    <![CDATA[ Stockholm ]]>
                </text>
            </location>
        </locations>
        <video>
            <content/>
            <url/>
        </video>
        <urls>
            <apply>
                <![CDATA[ https://emp.jobylon.com/applications/jobs/7161/create/ ]]>
            </apply>
            <ad>
                <![CDATA[ https://emp.jobylon.com/jobs/7161-kry-qa-manager/ ]]>
            </ad>
        </urls>
        <skills>
            <![CDATA[ <p>You have:</p> <ul> <li>A couple of years experience of running a QA team and process.</li> <li>Good knowledge of best practices in QA and agile testing.</li> <li>Experience of coaching your colleagues and working with change management across multiple teams.</li> <li>Some coding skills.</li> <li>Experience working with unit testing, automated test frameworks, continuous integration and continuous delivery pipelines.</li> <li>Experience from using cloud platforms, preferably AWS.</li> </ul> ]]>
        </skills>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>7160</id>
        <categories/>
        <company>
            <website>
                <![CDATA[ https://kry.se/ ]]>
            </website>
            <id>382</id>
            <name>
                <![CDATA[ KRY ]]>
            </name>
            <industry>
                <![CDATA[ Startup ]]>
            </industry>
            <logo>
                <![CDATA[ https://media-eu.jobylon.com/companies/company-logo/kry/12028784_909346472481867_4639286357079341408_o.712ec284.png ]]>
            </logo>
            <cover>
                <![CDATA[ https://media-eu.jobylon.com/jobs/company-cover/software-developer/img_9146.266527b7.JPG ]]>
            </cover>
            <slug>
                <![CDATA[ kry ]]>
            </slug>
            <descr>
                <![CDATA[ <p><strong><em>Join us in making healthcare better and more accessible to all!</em></strong></p> <p>KRY is a service where patients meet healthcare professionals through their phone or tablet.</p> <p>We who work at KRY want to build a better and more accessible healthcare by moving it online and by providing a service that gives the patient the best possible health care experience. We already have tens of thousands of happy users in Sweden and are now expanding internationally.</p> ]]>
            </descr>
        </company>
        <contact>
            <photo>
                <![CDATA[ https://media-eu.jobylon.com/main_contact/kry_2780_2.8d0c3a53.jpg ]]>
            </photo>
            <phone/>
            <email>
                <![CDATA[ joachim@kry.se ]]>
            </email>
            <name>
                <![CDATA[ Joachim Hedenius ]]>
            </name>
        </contact>
        <departments/>
        <title>
            <![CDATA[ Software developer ]]>
        </title>
        <slug>
            <![CDATA[ software-developer ]]>
        </slug>
        <descr>
            <![CDATA[ <p><strong>You will:</strong></p> <ul> <li>Work with all parts of the system across our full technology stack.</li> <li>Contribute in all stages in the product lifecycle: design, implementation, testing, deployment and maintenance.</li> <li>Build our backend services using Java 8 and the reactive toolkit Vert.x.</li> <li>Build our native iOS and Android apps using Swift and Java.</li> <li>Build our web interfaces using JavaScript with tools such as grunt, require and backbone.</li> <li>Deploy and operate our systems on Amazon AWS.</li> <li>Work in a lightweight scrum process where we constantly streamline our tools and workflows making sure that each workday is productive and stimulating.</li> </ul> ]]>
        </descr>
        <function>
            <![CDATA[ Software Development ]]>
        </function>
        <experience>
            <![CDATA[ Mid level ]]>
        </experience>
        <employment_type>
            <![CDATA[ Full-time ]]>
        </employment_type>
        <from_date>2016-12-02</from_date>
        <to_date/>
        <language>
            <![CDATA[ en ]]>
        </language>
        <locations>
            <location>
                <text>
                    <![CDATA[ Stockholm ]]>
                </text>
            </location>
        </locations>
        <video>
            <content/>
            <url/>
        </video>
        <urls>
            <apply>
                <![CDATA[ https://emp.jobylon.com/applications/jobs/7160/create/ ]]>
            </apply>
            <ad>
                <![CDATA[ https://emp.jobylon.com/jobs/7160-kry-software-developer/ ]]>
            </ad>
        </urls>
        <skills>
            <![CDATA[ <ul> <li>You have broad technical knowledge and don’t mind working in all parts of a system.</li> <li>You are continuously learning new things and keeping up to date with new technology and best practices.</li> <li>You like to share your knowledge with others.</li> <li>You are positive and prestige free.</li> <li>You have worked a couple of years with software development. Probably with Java and JavaScript and/or developing mobile apps.</li> <li>You are familiar with development tools and concepts such as GIT and continuous integration/delivery.</li> <li>You have a basic understanding of cloud hosting and have probably used Amazon AWS.</li> <li>You like the idea of working in a rapidly growing startup environment.</li> </ul> <p>If you have the right personality for KRY it’s not necessary to have experience with all the technologies and tools we are working with, you will quickly come up to speed anyway!</p> ]]>
        </skills>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>6535</id>
        <categories/>
        <company>
            <website>
                <![CDATA[ https://www.fishbrain.com/ ]]>
            </website>
            <id>463</id>
            <name>
                <![CDATA[ FishBrain ]]>
            </name>
            <industry>
                <![CDATA[ Startup ]]>
            </industry>
            <logo>
                <![CDATA[ https://media-eu.jobylon.com/companies/company-logo/fishbrain/fishbrain.f5cfa5cd.png ]]>
            </logo>
            <cover>
                <![CDATA[ https://media-eu.jobylon.com/companies/company-cover/fishbrain/fishbraincover.d4d86108.png ]]>
            </cover>
            <slug>
                <![CDATA[ fishbrain ]]>
            </slug>
            <descr>
                <![CDATA[ <p><strong>About Us</strong></p> <p>We write job ads like this one. We make the world’s best fishing app. We care about the environment. And we have an amazing time together, day in and day out. Check us out at fishbrain.com!</p> ]]>
            </descr>
        </company>
        <contact>
            <photo/>
            <phone/>
            <email>
                <![CDATA[ jobs@fishbrain.com ]]>
            </email>
            <name>
                <![CDATA[ Sara Bjelkstam ]]>
            </name>
        </contact>
        <departments/>
        <title>
            <![CDATA[ Android Mobile Engineer ]]>
        </title>
        <slug>
            <![CDATA[ android-mobile-engineer ]]>
        </slug>
        <descr>
            <![CDATA[ <p><strong>Now tell us if this is you </strong></p> <p>You appreciate and respect the outdoors. You might love fishing, or maybe hiking is more your speed. Most important is that you get exicted about working with amazing people solving challenging tasks.</p> <p>Are we getting close? If so, there's a good chance you should meet us!</p> <p><strong>This is the role </strong></p> <p>We are the next generation social network focused on one of the worlds biggest hobbies sport fishing. Only in the US there are more than 55 million people calling themselves anglers!</p> <p>We are a supercharged team of developers and we are looking forward to bring new coders in to increase the speed of our journey. Our Android app is used by hundreds of thousands of anglers on a daily basis. You will join as one of three core members of our Android team. You will have large responsibilities from day one. What you do will have actual impact on our users and Fishbrain as a company. Your opinions and ideas will matter.</p> <p><strong>Responsibilities </strong></p> <p><strong>Design and build </strong>advanced applications for the Android platform.<br> <strong>Produce </strong>high quality software using TDD, that's checked in regularly for continuous integration. <strong>Collaborate </strong>with crossfunctional teams to define, design, and ship new features.</p> <p>We’re looking for a talented Android developer with a big passion for development in general and mobile development in particular. As an Android developer you will be a key player in the development of the platform that Fishbrain is today.</p> <p><strong>Working with us </strong></p> <p>Our office is in city center of Stockholm, Sweden. The office has walls, windows, multiple coffee machines, and a team of fun and amazing people working inside it. It's also cubiclefree.</p> <p><strong>Our values </strong></p> <p><em>Fishing Responsibly</em></p> <p>For us, respecting the environment is about balance. We believe in catch &amp; release and the sustainable harvest of fish species. Because when it comes to the outdoors, tomorrow matters too.</p> <p><em>Fishing Is Better with Buddies</em></p> <p>We believe that it's more fun to brag about a catch with people who care about fishing. These people are often called anglers. You may think that's obvious, being an angler yourself. But on Fishbrain, your catch doesn't go headtohead with cats doing backflips, or toddlers feeding chocolate cake to their baby sisters.</p> <p><em>Fishing Smarter, Not Harder</em></p> <p>Don't get us wrong we're all for hard work, predawn wake ups to get to a fishing spot, and getting our hands dirty. But if there's a smarter way to fish, we're on it. It means we do the hard work of crunching catch numbers so you don't have to.</p> ]]>
        </descr>
        <function>
            <![CDATA[ Engineering ]]>
        </function>
        <experience>
            <![CDATA[ Entry level ]]>
        </experience>
        <employment_type>
            <![CDATA[ Full-time ]]>
        </employment_type>
        <from_date>2016-10-24</from_date>
        <to_date/>
        <language>
            <![CDATA[ en ]]>
        </language>
        <locations>
            <location>
                <text>
                    <![CDATA[ Stockholm, Sweden ]]>
                </text>
                <city_short>
                    <![CDATA[ Stockholm ]]>
                </city_short>
                <area_2_short>
                    <![CDATA[ Stockholm ]]>
                </area_2_short>
                <area_1_short>
                    <![CDATA[ Stockholm County ]]>
                </area_1_short>
                <city>
                    <![CDATA[ Stockholm ]]>
                </city>
                <area_2>
                    <![CDATA[ Stockholm ]]>
                </area_2>
                <area_1>
                    <![CDATA[ Stockholm County ]]>
                </area_1>
                <place_id>
                    <![CDATA[ ChIJywtkGTF2X0YRZnedZ9MnDag ]]>
                </place_id>
                <url>
                    <![CDATA[ https://maps.google.com/?q=Stockholm,+Sweden&ftid=0x465f763119640bcb:0xa80d27d3679d7766 ]]>
                </url>
                <country>
                    <![CDATA[ Sweden ]]>
                </country>
                <country_short>
                    <![CDATA[ SE ]]>
                </country_short>
            </location>
        </locations>
        <video>
            <content/>
            <url/>
        </video>
        <urls>
            <apply>
                <![CDATA[ https://emp.jobylon.com/applications/jobs/6535/create/ ]]>
            </apply>
            <ad>
                <![CDATA[ https://emp.jobylon.com/jobs/6535-fishbrain-android-mobile-engineer/ ]]>
            </ad>
        </urls>
        <skills>
            <![CDATA[ <p>Preferably a Bachelor's degree and/or MSc in Computer Science or equivalent experience.</p> <p>You are comfortable working with <strong>Java, Android, TDD, Git, Continuous Integration, Open Source, RESTful APIs </strong>and dealing with <strong>UI/UX </strong>challenges.</p> <p>You feel comfortable working in <strong>Agile environments </strong>with plenty of things going on and release cycles of two weeks.</p> <p><strong>A fast learner.</strong> Unless you're an expert in all the above, you'll need to pick up a few things along the way!</p> <p><strong>Handson</strong>. You prefer doing over talking. You can't wait to write code.</p> ]]>
        </skills>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>3496</id>
        <categories/>
        <company>
            <website>
                <![CDATA[ https://www.fishbrain.com/ ]]>
            </website>
            <id>463</id>
            <name>
                <![CDATA[ FishBrain ]]>
            </name>
            <industry>
                <![CDATA[ Startup ]]>
            </industry>
            <logo>
                <![CDATA[ https://media-eu.jobylon.com/companies/company-logo/fishbrain/fishbrain.f5cfa5cd.png ]]>
            </logo>
            <cover>
                <![CDATA[ https://media-eu.jobylon.com/companies/company-cover/fishbrain/fishbraincover.d4d86108.png ]]>
            </cover>
            <slug>
                <![CDATA[ fishbrain ]]>
            </slug>
            <descr>
                <![CDATA[ <p>We are the world-leading social network for anglers (professional and amateur enthusiast fishermen and women) with over 1 million users on our iOS and Android apps. We help our anglers to catch more and bigger fish and give them a chance to brag about it! Over the last year, we have been featured in AppStore, Forbes, TechCrunch, Bloomberg, VentureBeat, etc.</p> <p>Our team consists of more than 20 talented and fun people from all around the world, located in Stockholm.</p> ]]>
            </descr>
        </company>
        <contact>
            <photo/>
            <phone/>
            <email>
                <![CDATA[ jobs@fishbrain.com ]]>
            </email>
            <name>
                <![CDATA[ Sara Bjelkstam ]]>
            </name>
        </contact>
        <departments/>
        <title>
            <![CDATA[ Platform Engineer (Golang, Ruby on Rails) ]]>
        </title>
        <slug>
            <![CDATA[ platform-engineer-golang-ruby-on-rails ]]>
        </slug>
        <descr>
            <![CDATA[ <p>We’re the next generation social network focused on sport fishing. Our platform deals with millions of anglers contributing to the community on a daily basis.</p> <p>FishBrain's platform team designs, implements, and maintains scalable software architectures that are at the heart of our technology. The team moves fast and plays a pivotal role in ensuring the quality of the backend systems that power our Android and iOS apps.</p> <p>Responsibilities</p> <ul> <li> <p>Design, build, and deploy highly scalable software systems (including microservices) written in Ruby on Rails and Golang.</p> </li> <li> <p>Produce high quality software using TDD in a continuous delivery environment.</p> </li> <li> <p>Collaborate with cross-functional teams to define, design, and ship new features. Go deep into code reviews.</p> </li> </ul> ]]>
        </descr>
        <function>
            <![CDATA[ Engineering ]]>
        </function>
        <experience>
            <![CDATA[ Experienced ]]>
        </experience>
        <employment_type>
            <![CDATA[ Full-time ]]>
        </employment_type>
        <from_date>2016-03-09</from_date>
        <to_date/>
        <language>
            <![CDATA[ en ]]>
        </language>
        <locations>
            <location>
                <country>
                    <![CDATA[ Sverige ]]>
                </country>
                <city>
                    <![CDATA[ Stockholm ]]>
                </city>
                <area_2>
                    <![CDATA[ Stockholm ]]>
                </area_2>
                <text>
                    <![CDATA[ Stockholm, Sverige ]]>
                </text>
                <area_1>
                    <![CDATA[ Stockholms län ]]>
                </area_1>
            </location>
        </locations>
        <video>
            <content/>
            <url/>
        </video>
        <urls>
            <apply>
                <![CDATA[ https://emp.jobylon.com/applications/jobs/3496/create/ ]]>
            </apply>
            <ad>
                <![CDATA[ https://emp.jobylon.com/jobs/3496-fishbrain-platform-engineer-golang-ruby-on-rails/ ]]>
            </ad>
        </urls>
        <skills>
            <![CDATA[ <ul> <li> <p>Bachelor's degree and/or MSc in Computer Science or equivalent experience.</p> </li> <li> <p>Strong software engineering fundamentals, including data structures, design patterns, and complexity analysis.</p> </li> <li> <p>Fluency in an OOP language, such as Ruby, Java, C++, or similar (Ruby strongly preferred).</p> </li> <li> <p>Experience with RDBMS as well as NoSQL databases. Operating system internals, networking, and file systems are a plus.</p> </li> <li> <p>You're smart, get stuff done, have great energy, and thrive in a fast-paced startup environment.</p> </li> </ul> ]]>
        </skills>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>2884</id>
        <categories/>
        <company>
            <website>
                <![CDATA[ http://www.getfanzone.com/ ]]>
            </website>
            <id>381</id>
            <name>
                <![CDATA[ Fanzone ]]>
            </name>
            <industry>
                <![CDATA[ Startup ]]>
            </industry>
            <logo>
                <![CDATA[ https://media-eu.jobylon.com/companies/company-logo/fanzone/logo.2e385388.jpg ]]>
            </logo>
            <cover>
                <![CDATA[ https://media-eu.jobylon.com/companies/company-cover/fanzone/nfl3.4f1b040d.jpg ]]>
            </cover>
            <slug>
                <![CDATA[ fanzone ]]>
            </slug>
            <descr>
                <![CDATA[ <p>Fanzone is a platform for professional athletes to help them in digital and social channels. Our tool is focused on enabling these athletes with creating content, get actionable analytics and monetize their fan base. We love sports and want to bring the fan closer to their favorite players through these digital channels. A small fast-paced team with seed investment secured and working at SUP46 in central Stockholm.</p> ]]>
            </descr>
        </company>
        <contact>
            <photo>
                <![CDATA[ https://media-eu.jobylon.com/avatars/jacob4/3.%20Jobbbild.jpg ]]>
            </photo>
            <phone/>
            <email>
                <![CDATA[ jacob@getfanzone.com ]]>
            </email>
            <name>
                <![CDATA[ Jacob Leander-Olsson ]]>
            </name>
        </contact>
        <departments/>
        <title>
            <![CDATA[ Sales manager in Sweden ]]>
        </title>
        <slug>
            <![CDATA[ sales-manager-in-sweden ]]>
        </slug>
        <descr>
            <![CDATA[ <p>We are looking for our first sales manager who will be responsible for creating, identifying and closing sales within our sports network. The ideal candidate is a relationship builder, have a strong passions for sports, a creative mindset and 2-3 years of online sales experience. The candidate would also have a track record of sales hunting and good network among advertisers and/or athletes.</p> <p><strong>Responsibilities</strong></p> <ul> <li>Drive new revenue streams.</li> <li>Work with our network of players to identify relevant advertisers and creative ideas for potential deals. Also recruitment of new athletes to our network.</li> <li>Close deals with relevant advertisers and agencies, which have been generated through your professional network and cold-calling efforts.</li> <li>Help recruit and build sales team as we grow, including setting up sales process and framework for the sales organization.</li> <li>Ambassador for Fanzone towards the advertising market.</li> </ul> ]]>
        </descr>
        <function>
            <![CDATA[ Sales ]]>
        </function>
        <experience>
            <![CDATA[ Mid level ]]>
        </experience>
        <employment_type>
            <![CDATA[ Full-time ]]>
        </employment_type>
        <from_date>2016-02-01</from_date>
        <to_date/>
        <language>
            <![CDATA[ en ]]>
        </language>
        <locations>
            <location>
                <country>
                    <![CDATA[ Sverige ]]>
                </country>
                <city>
                    <![CDATA[ Stockholm ]]>
                </city>
                <area_2>
                    <![CDATA[ Stockholm ]]>
                </area_2>
                <text>
                    <![CDATA[ Stockholm, Sverige ]]>
                </text>
                <area_1>
                    <![CDATA[ Stockholms län ]]>
                </area_1>
            </location>
        </locations>
        <video>
            <content/>
            <url/>
        </video>
        <urls>
            <apply>
                <![CDATA[ https://emp.jobylon.com/applications/jobs/2884/create/ ]]>
            </apply>
            <ad>
                <![CDATA[ https://emp.jobylon.com/jobs/2884-fanzone-sales-manager-in-sweden/ ]]>
            </ad>
        </urls>
        <skills>
            <![CDATA[ <ul> <li>2-3 years of online digital sales experience with deep knowledge of digital products, advertising, social media and content.</li> <li>Humble and driven salesperson. Great attitude, team player and relationship builder.</li> <li>Creative mindset with creating and conceptualizing campaigns. Initially done yourself but later on by dedicated creative talents internally.</li> <li>Passion for sports and bonus points if existing relationship with talented athletes.</li> <li>Strong social skills and outstanding client relationship.</li> <li>Entrepreneurial attitude and want to work in a fast-paced startup environment.</li> <li>Fluent in Swedish and English. </li> </ul> ]]>
        </skills>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>2485</id>
        <categories/>
        <company>
            <website>
                <![CDATA[ http://www.getfanzone.com/ ]]>
            </website>
            <id>381</id>
            <name>
                <![CDATA[ Fanzone ]]>
            </name>
            <industry>
                <![CDATA[ Startup ]]>
            </industry>
            <logo>
                <![CDATA[ https://media-eu.jobylon.com/companies/company-logo/fanzone/logo.2e385388.jpg ]]>
            </logo>
            <cover>
                <![CDATA[ https://media-eu.jobylon.com/companies/company-cover/fanzone/top2.82f49062.jpg ]]>
            </cover>
            <slug>
                <![CDATA[ fanzone ]]>
            </slug>
            <descr>
                <![CDATA[ <p>Fanzone is a platform for professional athletes to help them in digital and social channels. Our tool is focused on enabling these athletes with creating content, get actionable analytics and monetize their fan base. We love sports and want to bring the fan closer to their favorite players through these digital channels. A small fast-paced team with seed investment secured and working at SUP46 in central Stockholm.</p> ]]>
            </descr>
        </company>
        <contact>
            <photo>
                <![CDATA[ https://media-eu.jobylon.com/avatars/jacob4/3.%20Jobbbild.jpg ]]>
            </photo>
            <phone/>
            <email>
                <![CDATA[ jacob@getfanzone.com ]]>
            </email>
            <name>
                <![CDATA[ Jacob Leander-Olsson ]]>
            </name>
        </contact>
        <departments/>
        <title>
            <![CDATA[ Back-end developer with Node.js and MongoDB experience ]]>
        </title>
        <slug>
            <![CDATA[ back-end-developer-with-nodejs-and-mongodb-experience ]]>
        </slug>
        <descr>
            <![CDATA[ <p>We are looking for a back-end developer to work with our analytics tool and content management system. The back-end consists of the presentation layer, fetching data from the social networks (Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, YouTube), posting content to the same networks and set of internal API’s. We do collect a lot of data and later on will be expanded to include reach calculations, sentiment analysis and demographics. Built on Node.js and MongoDB.</p> <p>You need to be a product-aware developer who loves to build scalable products and appreciate great user interfaces. You should thrive to work in a startup environment with quick prototyping and rapid iterations. In return, you will get a lot of responsibilities from day one and a great opportunity to help shape the future product roadmap. Employment with fixed salary and a possibility for stock options.</p> ]]>
        </descr>
        <function>
            <![CDATA[ Engineering ]]>
        </function>
        <experience>
            <![CDATA[ Mid level ]]>
        </experience>
        <employment_type>
            <![CDATA[ Full-time ]]>
        </employment_type>
        <from_date>2016-01-07</from_date>
        <to_date/>
        <language>
            <![CDATA[ en ]]>
        </language>
        <locations>
            <location>
                <country>
                    <![CDATA[ Sverige ]]>
                </country>
                <city>
                    <![CDATA[ Stockholm ]]>
                </city>
                <area_2>
                    <![CDATA[ Stockholm ]]>
                </area_2>
                <text>
                    <![CDATA[ Stockholm, Sverige ]]>
                </text>
                <area_1>
                    <![CDATA[ Stockholms län ]]>
                </area_1>
            </location>
        </locations>
        <video>
            <content/>
            <url/>
        </video>
        <urls>
            <apply>
                <![CDATA[ https://emp.jobylon.com/applications/jobs/2485/create/ ]]>
            </apply>
            <ad>
                <![CDATA[ https://emp.jobylon.com/jobs/2485-fanzone-back-end-developer-with-nodejs-and-mongodb-experience/ ]]>
            </ad>
        </urls>
        <skills>
            <![CDATA[ <ul> <li>Experience in back-end development with JavaScript, Node.js and MongoDB.</li> <li>Strong programming skills writing scalable code, comfortable working with agile methodologies, RESTful API’s and Git.</li> <li>Great if you have worked against Facebook, Twitter, YouTube and/or Instagram’s API previously.</li> <li>Entrepreneurial attitude and want to work in a fast-paced startup environment.</li> <li>Fluent in English, both written and verbal.</li> <li>Plus if you have a passion for sports!</li> </ul> ]]>
        </skills>
    </job>
</jobs>